<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SQL on A6k</title>
    <link>https://localhost:1313/techs/sql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SQL on A6k</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>© A6k</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/techs/sql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackbox</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/blackbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/blackbox/</guid>
      <description>Tracking trains on UK network. Processing messages from external systems. Maintaining internal data stores. Api’s to drive customer facing displays and control room. Driving automated announcements with speech synthesis through a custom service to on site devices. Tested via emulation in software. Azure, ServiceFabric, redis, cosmosdb, service bus, sql, c#, aspnetcore, akka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artesian Solutions</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/artesian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/artesian/</guid>
      <description>Uses a taxonomy to tag and categorise content. Users are supplied with relevant stories that allow them to engage with their prospects and customers. Also provides access to company information, both to individual companies and via segmentation/faceting to isolate a prospect list.
Joined at inception. Created or collaborated on core services. Raw content retrieved by custom spider and via 3rd parties. Taxonomy and content processing. Custom syntax and parsing. Distributed processing mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprimo</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/aprimo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/aprimo/</guid>
      <description>Then ltd purchased by Aprimo. I moved to Indianapolis to incorporate Then&#39;s Asset Management system into their marketing product. Concerns about LGPL licensed libraries required the writing of a PDF parsing and manipulation library direct from the specs. Introduced Subversion. Also involved in building and supporting new features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Then Ltd</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/then/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/then/</guid>
      <description>Introduced dotnet, C#, Asp.net. Developed customer facing web UI for storing, editing and scaling PDFs. Responsible for internal machines, servers and network including exposing the app to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>