<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photoshop on A6k</title>
    <link>https://localhost:1313/designs/photoshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photoshop on A6k</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>© A6k</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://localhost:1313/designs/photoshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Codit/SwissRe</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/codit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/codit/</guid>
      <description>Uses authoritative sources to monitor events such as earthquakes and cyclones to automatically payout when the event matches the policy criteria. no human in the loop.
As a team member I worked on many parts of the system: api&#39;s; message handlers; catastrophe impact calculation; policy processing; automated testing; deployment pipelines …
Azure, net46+, dotnetCore, ServiceBus, AppServices, LogicApps, Api’s, caching, messaging, vsts, git</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Radio</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/globalradio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/globalradio/</guid>
      <description>Asp.net WebApi, Angular2, TypeScript, Kendo, dapper, SqlServer, CQS, RabbitMQ. Resolved several performance issues (mainly threading and async). Reworked backend framework, services and build system to improve DRYness and reduce developer friction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connections Education</title>
      <link>https://localhost:1313/cv/connectionseducation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost:1313/cv/connectionseducation/</guid>
      <description>Member of a remote virtual team. Working within clients agile processes and closely with several project teams. Involved in several aspects of updating CEs online education systems. Gitflow based development within VSTS. HttpClient based proxy for internal and external services. Custom formatters and serializers. Protection from async deadlocks. Integrated 3rd party api via Azure ServiceBus to internal systems. Created testing and mocking frameworks for testing services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>